all
right I guess let's do another state of
the stream
address in my like wrinkled shirt look
at my shirt's wrinkled you know why do
you know why cuz it was right in that
bin right there until I pulled it out
and put it on
mhm yeah I know it's not I'm not it's it
doesn't look good it doesn't look good
but I have a plan I have a plan so that
my clothing looks more or you know less
like I just got off of a of
a of a of a
thing this is the mug for the day
compliments of Doris capner doris. buy
your mug
today I don't think she has any more for
sale you know I I made an announcement
that that that she was selling [__]
mugs before and everybody wanted one and
she's like nope
sorry because she didn't feel like
making him she could she was making like
stuff for her gallery
show so so what is this video about this
video is about us me artx Rob and the
stream I'm going to keep doing a state
of the stream address um mostly because
people have so many questions about like
what what are we doing you know and I'm
going to go ahead if you have questions
about the stream and what we're doing
what the community is doing this is the
place to ask those questions um but
sometimes I'm just going to make a
random video uh to talk about it because
as you know there's been a lot of people
are following the robin Doris show you
know you know they're kind of following
it and they want to know what's going on
and so I thought I'd catch everybody up
plus it's something I can post to
Facebook yeah uh how you doing hey Mama
Mama meow how are you thank you for your
comments yesterday Sam would love to
meet you she's fantastic dog there's G
to be a lot more Sam on the Stream
So after yesterday yesterday was rather
an interesting day uh if the VOD had to
be deleted because I doxed stuff about
myself I don't want you to
know um so that's not around but you
know there was lots of other things
including a nice crash had a nice
wonderful crash in a rainstorm it was
awesome didn't lose any teeth on that
one it was kind of a slow motion crash
there's a clip of
that
and you know I I've been struggling
because there's been a lot of a lot of
things happened yesterday something else
happened yesterday that I can't really
talk about it
involves a hospital and one of my
children um I can't talk about that I
don't want to dox the details of that at
all
um so yeah and uh and um trying to think
of something else now
uh so yeah and and and my phone my phone
died my phone died so right in the time
when you know I can't use it it's still
doing its thing look at it look at it's
got a mind of its own it's like see what
it's doing it's like doing whatever the
hell at once everyone wanted to like
click on everything so um not sure why
the phone is completely dead but it is
dead so that it's kind of funny because
I was streaming and my stream was still
working but I couldn't control the
stream in fact got raided I got raided
right by ugly one of my good good
friends best one of my best puds on
Twitch U I'm very happy to count ugly
among my my friends and peers um I'm
just so impressed by everything she's
doing with her mountain biking streaming
up in New Jersey she's just breaking new
ground up there literally breaking new
ground literally breaking new ground
like cutting trees down and taking rocks
out breaking new ground making new
trails she's just amazing and she raided
and and then I was you know I
crashed and my phone went flying off the
front went flying off the front of my
bike of Nina back here um and and it
uh
ouch yeah so I got a little road
rash this here is Nina this
here that's Nina biting me
now yesterday for no reason at all Nina
fell over and the chain ring just went
and it just like ground my leg so I'm
going to take a break from the bike
today but don't worry there's other
things going on so so I crashed I
crashed on the bike it was just a just a
really slow motion
thing uh it makes life so much more I
mean you know anyway it's fine it's all
good and the worst part of this though
is on the same day that I learned about
the child Hospital thing my phone
stopped working that day in fact I got a
call and I couldn't answer it I so at
you know at 10:00 I have an appointment
with the Verizon I'm going to go back
there and get my phone
replaced I don't know how much that's
going to cost which brings me to another
major
topic um
money
so um even though I make a lot of money
and and my wife is making a lot of money
too for what she does um we are
still not going to be able to do the
house thing and we're also not going to
be able to do the apartment
thing um there's just too many things
going on right now including really
substantial insurance insance
payments uh both for my teeth and
for you know my children uh that are
they just every time something happens
my my you know my son's you know my wife
totaled two cars in a row over the last
two years and then um you know we so and
then you know my my stepson's computer
just died uh we co-signed to help our
other son buy a
car um you know and it's just been a
mess plus we're still paying off a tax
lean because of a bad accountant that we
had and a bunch of other side you don't
need to know all the details the bottom
line is is it's you know we're
we're right where's my cup [__] it right
so even though we're we're incomer we're
not um you know we just we just can't we
can't think about big substantial 30,000
down payments right now we just
can't I paid 10 grand for a new car two
years ago out of cash and um my wife
total it within a
year um plus you know my wife's paying
quite a bit of money for her studio
apartment that she had and not an
Apartments where her artist and stuff
definitely been happening lately I
believe P up here I mean you know things
are things and um
again this is the state of the stream
it's kind of the robin dor show segment
number 25 or something so so that's
what's going on I do want to kind of
just there is some good light at the end
of the tunnel um
and yeah I mean the whole fact that
we're even in this apartment is largely
because of just life happening you know
covid happened and all this just tons of
stuff have happened for the most part
though I am very very well off and so
I'm not worried I'm not worried I really
am not I'm not I'm sometimes I worry
about being able to to help my
kids you know stuff like that anyway I'm
sure my wife is listening she probably
doesn't want me to talk about this she's
going to turn on the phone she like what
is he going to say um the biggest
takeaway from here this is we decided
that we're not going to move and we're
not going to go to an apartment um even
a new house we were going to rent a new
home and we looked at the money for that
and we're like I don't know if we're
going to even be needed yet and then I
talked to one of my kids and they're
like well I really don't if I come it's
going to be for a little while it's not
going to be to live with you or
something so they don't really need the
space and so they're like well do we
really need the space so then we got
thinking about H what's going the real
problem was we don't have any space here
so does anybody want to guess what the
answer
is this is going to happen today and
tomorrow and over the
weekend I'm going to go upgrade the I'm
going to go upgrade the storage unit so
right now we have a tiny little storage
unit that does not back up to the the
driving area some of you know some of
youve seen the storage unit that we have
and basically I'm going to rent a
garage and I'll be streaming from the
garage I'll be
streaming uh bike maintenance from the
garage I I hope I hope I hope that they
have a spigot with water so I can
actually spray down my bikes and stuff
like that I mean after this is another
reason this this has been coming about
is because yesterday
yesterday and the day before I've been
getting into muddy bike riding and I'm
like hey I can do this I can stream this
and then I tried to bring these cars
garage cam absolutely there's going to
definitely be a garage cam absolutely
multiple garage cams actually I have two
three four I have six action
cameras hey how you doing I have six
action cameras so I can easily set up
those cameras in that
garage um
I don't think they have Wi-Fi there God
if they had Wi-Fi that would be so
good if they had Wi-Fi even a even a bad
Wi-Fi bottom line so I'm going to move
this and all of the the the the our
front room right now remember all those
red things they're all in the front room
there's no place to do anything so that
means we're going to be able to do yoga
both in the in in here and probably in
the other room so I'm going to start
doing yoga again I'm going to start
doing uh music again I'll probably dance
the 80s dance night again um my phone is
not working no my phone is dead so I got
to go get a new
one um so that's happening today 10: I'm
not going to stream that I'm just going
to go do that because it's too
risky um but then so this this today and
tomorrow I'm going to move everything in
this apartment into the new storage unit
and another thing too about the storage
unit is it potentially means I can buy a
used I'm not going to buy a new one I
can buy a used paddle board so that we
can have that in the storage unit um and
then I just so The New Normal is going
to be me taking the taking subu taking
her to the storage unit deciding what
fun things to do today grabbing the hab
Habachi so we can go to the park and
make Stakes or something and and then
packing up packing up the Subaru like
like every other good red-blooded
American I'll take my super I'll be I'll
do the normal American thing you drive
to your storage unit where you have way
too much stuff that you don't need and
you load it up with all your outdoor
stuff and then you go have a weekend of
Adventure and then you come back and you
unload it all and then you go back home
that's going to be the new
normal so that means I won't have to do
bike maintenance on the carpet in my
master bedroom it means that um you know
Sam will have a place to lay her head
when the thunderstorms hit it means that
uh you know I I thought about setting up
that back patio and doing it out there
um but I changed my mind about that
because it's just too much we one of my
bikes already got stolen off the back
patio
so so that's that's the new normal um I
am going to be um doing a lot more
co-working DJ stuff um
and going through the music and stuff um
I it's it is I think it's going to be
really I'm super excited because I get
to design it I get to I get to make the
garage like fun you know what I mean
like in fact I've been thinking about it
I've been thinking
about I've been thinking about taking
some of
my I mean it really depends on how much
internet access we have there
honestly I'm going to make it kind of as
a secondary streaming location because I
can still stream from there even though
I have OBS here which is something I've
been practicing right I want to figure
out how to practice stream this is this
is good on so many levels for for the
stream because because what I can do is
I can I can practice streaming from the
rig with a
laptop and a good mic so this is another
thing I want I this has kind of been
inspired by some of the other streamers
I've been watching recently but they
have really really really great mics on
the road they go on on the road and they
and I have my Scarlet my Scarlet's this
little USB um you know board like this
one and you take the scarlet and you can
put any anything in there right you can
and I actually took it with the with
this here that studio there's a studio
mic back there so I can get ready I can
get used to taking the laptop and doing
that that kind of stuff
um and then streaming it that
way uh I'm trying to decide
what I'm honestly I think I think I
might be able to pull it off just with
the Bell box because the Bell box has
USB audio
in I have all the gear for this and I
haven't been using it I want to try this
so I've got I've got USB audio
in
on you know God you know what I just
realized the transmitter can take a USB
input
uh-huh I wonder if the DJI mics can take
a transmitter input do you know what I
you know you know what I could do with
that I could make those
mics independent so I could take this
mic I could take any mic connect to and
then plug it into the sh and then have
the sh plug into the DJI thing and then
have the Bell box be anywhere oh my Lord
yeah we need to look into that that that
could be really cool I mean one of the
things I I have wanted to do is I wanted
to start doing you know Open Mic stuff
again
um you know I I I love having really
good sound the the DJ mics which by the
way one of the transmitters is busted
it's like totally gone I mean it seems
to booed up earlier but I don't know if
it's going to work it got wet I have
insurance for that but we'll
see
hm I'm trying to think about this now
I'm trying to think about this now
because if we yeah anyway so suffice it
to say state of the stream uh lots more
live music we're going to be doing live
music uh I'm going to be playing more
music I'm going to be dejing more
because I absolutely love music it makes
me very happy um it's something I can do
no matter where I am even if I'm stuck
in a an
apartment and um you know that's the
thing
there's at least one of you out there
wondering what the the hell is going on
with the Boost so
yesterday uh a very well-meaning person
a new member to the stream asked when
are you going to fill the gaps in the
beginner boost and by gaps uh what they
mean is I'll show you let me just show
you so you can go
see um the beginner
boost
is is um the thing beginning overie is
here uh here's all the the stuff looks
like the family is waking up I can hear
them um the idea just for the beginner
boost in case you guys don't know this
already is that we would add stuff I
mean there's somebody said it was like a
1990s website perpetually under
construction I have avoided the under
construction L because I know about that
but the truth is I I didn't even want to
do a website until the whole thing was
done and I was like nope that'll never
happen so what we are doing is as we're
filling it out and I mean come on give
me a break look at how many Blues are
there you see that lots of blue there
yeah but people have finished all that
and they're like we want more we want
more uh and so I need to you know do
some of these other
videos uh and the idea of the Boost is
over the course of a year um all of this
stuff would get filled in so that you
know assuming I live through the year
knock on wood um that you know things
would there's really no reason for me to
die by the way I just don't like
planning so so so that's what's up with
the boo that this this stuff is coming a
promise um it's just I have to record it
uh I'm only I'm only recording it you
know a little bit every day uh or on the
weekend during the beginner boost time
which is at 11 o'clock on
Saturdays um this is where we do that
kind of thing
so so that's the plan my friends uh I'm
a happy camper I I am I yesterday I
started out pretty depressed and I ended
up rather and happy by the by the end of
the ride despite you know the 9-year-old
girl swelling at swearing at me through
the window and the crash and and the
loss of my phone and and my kid in the
hospital
and what are you going to
do that's what you're going to do right
there you're just going to you're just
going to say [__] it and you're going to
just keep trying you're just going to
take one step forward you're going to
listen to some great
music let's see if that's enough for me
to get taken
[Music]
down bye everybody